# Adralia Nelson Mandela

### Full Stack Software Engineer

I am passionate, problem solver, critical thinker and full stack software engineer with a passion for building systems and coming up with solutions for solving everyday challenges through technology. I hold a Bachelor's degree in Software Engineering from Makerere University With 3+ years of experience in software development.



nadralia@gmail.com

+256779003145/+256700188731

Ntinda, kampala, Uganda

linkedin.com/in/adralia-nelson-2a956564 in

live:nadralia S

github.com/nadralia 🚺

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### **Software Engineer** KainGroup

02/2020 - Present

Kampala

KAINGroup Ltd. is a total IT service delivery and consultancy company with a core staff that has vast experience. We build our confidence through sound fundamentals, proven history, and robust infrastructure. Committed to the highest standards of quality, customer care, and innovative solutions, we endeavor to deliver on every promise

Contact: Zack Atama - +256-751-070-199

## Associate Software engineer/Developer Andela Uganda

02/2019 - 11/2019

Kampala, Uganda

Andela is an African company that identifies and develops software developers.

### Achievements/Tasks

- At Andela, my first 3 months were spent building an app called Authors Haven in a team of 6 engineers using Django Rest Framework, React JS, Redux, PostgreSQL and Sequelize ORM. I was also able to develop an Ireporter web application using Python/Flask for the Backend and vanilla Javascript for the Frontend
- I recently worked as a member of a team building an external product called EzyAgric using Lumen, angular 7, circleCi, Docker and Jira

Contact: Oghenefejiro Okagbare Jason – (+2348077050792) and (+2347035981005)

# **Software Developer (MWH Foundation)**MWH FOUNDATION UGANDA

02/2018 - 10/2018

FADIS is a tool to strengthen the position of farmers in the agriculture value chain in order to improve business results

Contact: Martiin Deddens -

+31 6 24513426 (martijn.deddens@mwh-trust.com)

### **EDUCATION**

# **B.sc. Software Engineering** Makerere University

08/2012 - 01/2017

Kampala, Uganda

#### Courses

- Application
   Developement
- Software Reliability and Testing
- Database Management System
- Software Design Patterns

### **SKILLS**



### PERSONAL PROJECTS

WestNileTv (02/2016 - Present) 5

 WestNile Television Uganda is an Internet TV channel with all encompassing content, generated in categories of news, entrepreneurship, politics, edutainment, culture and tourism among others.

Ireporter (02/2018 − Present) 🗹

Corruption is a huge bane to Africa's development. African
countries must develop novel and localised solutions that will curb
this menace, hence the birth of iReporter. iReporter enables
any/every citizen to bring any form of corruption to the notice of
appropriate authorities and the general public. Users can also
report on things that needs government intervention.

Tims (Tour and Itinerary Management sytem) (02/2020 – Present) 

✓

 Tims is a software as a service for tour and itinerary management system

## **CERTIFICATES**

Udacity Nano Degree (FullStack Web Developer) (10/2019 – Present)

#### LANGUAGES

English

Lugbara

Full Professional Proficiency Professional Working Proficiency

### **INTERESTS**

Football Travelling Chess Movies

Agriculture Artificial Intelligence Politics